<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.free-astro.siril.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Siril</name>
  <summary>Astronomical image (pre-)processing program</summary>
  <translation type="gettext">siril</translation>
  <description>
    <p>Siril is an image processing tool specially tailored for noise reduction and improving the signal/noise ratio of an image from multiple captures, as required in astronomy.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar_DZ">Siril هو برنامج معالجة الصور المصممة خصيصا للحد من الضوضاء وتحسين نسبة الإشارة / الضوضاء صورة من يلتقط متعددة، كما هو مطلوب في علم الفلك</p>
    <p xml:lang="de_DE">Siril ist ein Bildbearbeitungsprogramm, das speziell auf die Geräuschreduzierung und Verbesserung des Signal-Rausch-Verhältnisses eines Bildes aus mehreren Aufnahmen abgestimmt ist, wie in der Astronomie erforderlich.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es_ES">Siril es una herramienta de procesado de imágenes especialmente diseñada para la reducción de ruido y la mejora del ratio señal/ruido de una imagen de múltiples capturas, como las requeridas en astronomía.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr_FR">Siril est un outil de traitement d'image spécialement adapté pour la réduction du bruit et l'amélioration du rapport signal/bruit des images astronomiques.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el_GR">Το Siril είναι ένα εργαλείο επεξεργασίας εικόνων ειδικά κατασκευασμένο για τη μείωση θορύβου και τη βελτίωση του λόγου σήματος/θορύβου μιας εικόνας από πολλαπλές λήψεις, όπως απαιτείται στην αστρονομία.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it_IT">Siril è uno strumento per l'elaborazione delle immagini adatto soprattutto per la riduzione del rumore e per migliorare il rapporto segnale/rumore di un'immagine a partire da acquisizioni multiple, come richiesto in astronomia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl_BE">Siril is een programme voor beeldbewerking, speciaal gericht op ruisvermindering en verhoging van het SNR van een afbeelding afkomstig van meerdere opnames, zoals vereist in astronomie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru_RU">Siril это инструмент обработки, специально разработанный для подавления шумов и улучшения отношения сигнал/шум с помощью сложения множества изображений.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">Siril是一款特殊的图像处理软件，专为天文摄影所需求的噪声消除和提高信噪比（多帧叠加）而定制。</p>
    <p>Siril can align automatically or manually, stack and enhance pictures from various file formats, even images sequences (movies and SER files).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar_DZ">Siril يمكن محاذاة ,تلقائيا أو يدويا ، وتعزيز الصور من صيغ الملفات المختلفة ، وحتى الصور متواليات ( الأفلام وملفات SER ) .</p>
    <p xml:lang="de_DE">Siril kann Bilder mit verschiedenen Dateiformaten und sogar Bildsequenzen (Filme und SER-Dateien) automatisch oder manuell ausrichten, stapeln und verbessern.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es_ES">Siril puede alinearl automática o manualmente, apilar y mejorar imágenes de varios formatos de fichero, incluso secuencias (películas y ficheros SER).</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr_FR">Siril peut aligner automatiquement ou manuellement, empiler et améliorer des images de différents formats aussi bien que des séquences d'images (films et fichiers SER).</p>
    <p xml:lang="el_GR">Το Siril μπορεί αυτόματα ή χειροκίνητα, να σωρεύσει και να ενισχύσει εικόνες από διάφορους τύπους αρχείων, ακόμα και από αλληλουχίες εικόνων (ταινίες και αρχεία SER).</p>
    <p xml:lang="it_IT">Siril può allineare automaticamente o manualmente, sommare e migliorare immagini a partire da vari formati di file, anche sequenze di immagini (filmati e file SER).</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl_BE">Siri kan automatisch of manueel beelden in talrijke formaten (zelfs video’s en SER bestanden) uitlijnen, stacken en verbeteren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru_RU">Siril умеет выравнивать автоматически и вручную, складывать и улучшать изображения различных форматов и последовательности (видеоролики и SER файлы).</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">Siril能够自动对齐和手动对齐，叠加和强化多种格式的图片，甚至是图片序列（视频和SER文件）。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://screenshots.debian.net/screenshots/000/014/985/large.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://screenshots.debian.net/screenshots/000/014/987/large.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://screenshots.debian.net/screenshots/000/014/986/large.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <provides>
    <binary>siril</binary>
  </provides>
  <url type="homepage">http://free-astro.org/index.php/Siril</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">http://free-astro.org/bugs/view_all_bug_page.php</url>
  <url type="help">http://free-astro.org/index.php/Siril:Manual</url>
  <update_contact>cyril_at_free-astro.org</update_contact>
</component>
